QUESTIONS = [{
  'id': 1,
  'question':
  'Which of the following is determined during the analysis phase of software development?',
  'answer_1': 'Fitness for purpose',
  'answer_2': 'Functional requirements',
  'answer_3': 'Pseudocode',
  'answer_4': 'Error Handling',
  'correct': 'answer_2'
}, {
  'id': 2,
  'question': 'Which of the following is a definition of a program input?',
  'answer_1': 'Data that will be entered by a user or received from a file',
  'answer_2':
  'Data that is to be initialised by the programmer during implementation and that will not change when the software is in use',
  'answer_3': 'Results of testing',
  'answer_4': 'Actual Parameters',
  'correct': 'answer_1'
}, {
  'id': 3,
  'question': 'Which of the following is a definition of a process?',
  'answer_1':
  'Code created to execute a sequence of instructions that may make use of inputs and may result in output to the user',
  'answer_2': 'Data received from a text file',
  'answer_3': 'Data sent to a printer',
  'answer_4': 'Syntax Error feedback',
  'correct': 'answer_1'
}, {
  'id': 4,
  'question': 'Which of the following is a definition of a program output?',
  'answer_1': 'Data that is validated after being entered by a user',
  'answer_2':
  'Data that is sent from the program to the user, a file or peripheral',
  'answer_3': 'Selection statements',
  'answer_4': 'Syntax Error feedback',
  'correct': 'answer_2'
}, {
  'id': 5,
  'question':
  'What would you consider when outlining assumptions about new software that is being developed?',
  'answer_1': 'Hardware needed to run the software',
  'answer_2': 'Data structures',
  'answer_3': 'Normal data',
  'answer_4': 'Character Encoding',
  'correct': 'answer_1'
}, {
  'id': 6,
  'question':
  'Why is it important to identify appropriate project boundaries during the software analysis phase?',
  'answer_1': 'So that what is entered into the program will work properly',
  'answer_2': 'So that a program doesnâ€™t use too much memory',
  'answer_3': 'So that it is sure what it is doing',
  'answer_4':
  'So that the client cannot add new functionality requirements during the project development without incurring additional cost implications',
  'correct': 'answer_4'
}, {
  'id': 7,
  'question':
  'Which of the following statements best describes the Purpose of a project during the analysis stage',
  'answer_1':
  'A list of what will be delivered to the client at the end of the project',
  'answer_2': 'A list of what will and will not be included in the project',
  'answer_3': 'A definition of the projects inputs, processes and outputs',
  'answer_4':
  'The reason for the project including the client or end user needs',
  'correct': 'answer_4'
}, {
  'id': 8,
  'question':
  'Which of the following statements best describes the Functional Requirements of a project during the analysis stage',
  'answer_1':
  'A list of what will be delivered to the client at the end of the project',
  'answer_2': 'A list of what will and will not be included in the project',
  'answer_3': 'A definition of the projects inputs, processes and outputs',
  'answer_4':
  'The reason for the project including the client or end user needs',
  'correct': 'answer_3'
}, {
  'id': 9,
  'question':
  'Which of the following statements best describes the Scope of a project during the analysis stage',
  'answer_1':
  'A list of what will be delivered to the client at the end of the project',
  'answer_2': 'A list of what will and will not be included in the project',
  'answer_3': 'A definition of the projects inputs, processes and outputs',
  'answer_4':
  'The reason for the project including the client or end user needs',
  'correct': 'answer_1'
}, {
  'id': 10,
  'question':
  'Which of the following statements best describes the Boundary of a project during the analysis stage',
  'answer_1':
  'A list of what will be delivered to the client at the end of the project',
  'answer_2': 'A list of what will and will not be included in the project',
  'answer_3': 'A definition of the projects inputs, processes and outputs',
  'answer_4':
  'The reason for the project including the client or end user needs',
  'correct': 'answer_2'
}]